{
    "id": "8d93ff3872794238b2870b66dbb9b83e",
    "title": "Prepositions Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There were ……………… twenty people at the lecture.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She passed the exam ………………….. her teacher.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He can’t watch the film because he is still …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "below"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The climbers stopped about 200 meters ………………….. the top of the mountain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "under",
                "below",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She went to work ……………… her illness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "in spite of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is writing a book ………………… Hindu philosophy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is anxious ..................... her health.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I can run 400 meters ………………. about 60 seconds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They congratulated her ……………… her success.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents never showed if they were disappointed ………………. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}